(Beijing)
(Ritan Hot Pot)
Hello.
Long time no see.
How are you doing?
I'm good.
Pretty good.
How is it going?
What have you been up to
in Beijing lately?
Just messing around.
Just wandering around
and rehearsing.
When was the last time you saw Xuan?
The last time I saw Xuan
was the day the three of us,
me, you and Ruita,
had dinner together.
The day we had dinner together.
(Zhou Youling arrives at the restaurant)
Half a month.
What's up?
Hello.
Youling.
Youling is coming.
Hello.
Come on, sit.
Big Bro.
Big Bro, I haven't seen you for ages.
Why are you all looking
so handsome today?
You look like you just woke up.
No.
I sat on the ground the whole way here.
No, you really...
I thought you were joking.
I'm serious.
I failed to get a standby ticket.
I had no seat for 3.5 hours.
I totally know how that feels.
I once stood for 4.5 hours
without a seat.
Did you just sit on the ground?
I sat on my suitcase.
It was okay.
That's not too bad then.
Have you ordered yet?
Not yet.
We each have our own hot pot.
Just choose your preferred
broth base.
Clear broth is fine.
Youling, what broth do you want?
Clear broth.
Three clear broths.
Waiter.
We're ready to order.
Hello, I'm the waitress.
What would you like to order?
What do you want to eat?
I'll take your order.
Didn't you eat the escargots?
Yeah, this is my second meal.
I'm having my second round of hot pot.
You're messing with me.
(Best spot for the drama)
What are you doing?
(Filmed on Zhou Youling's phone)
(Earlier today)
Zhou Youling and I originally planned
to go to Beijing together.
I kept it a secret from Xiao Wentao.
I told him I wasn't coming.
And now, look what happened.
Zhou Youling completely missed
his high-speed train.
(Jia Peixuan arrived in Beijing)
I finally arrived.
It's already 7 PM.
5.5 hours. I'm totally worn out.
Who is actually in Beijing?
I finally met up with Zhou Youling.
We're almost
at the restaurant now.
We're here.
I want to bite you.
You can do it. It's fine.
Don't edit this part in.
I heard her voice when she came in,
and I thought it sounded familiar.
You even directly...
You want to directly...
You were sitting with your back to me.
I was wondering...
This spot is perfect.
Yeah.
I was just thinking it was nice
that he was sitting with his back to me.
Youling, did you know she was coming?
Obviously, I brought her along.
I knew as well.
You knew she was...
Of course, I knew.
You two are really something.
See. We have a group chat
with only five people.
Now we can add him to the group.
The group chat without Xiao Wentao.
We can add you to the group now.
Okay.
You know. Sometimes,
I asked Youling something,
but he didn't reply to me.
I just can't figure out why.
He didn't know how to reply.
I wanted to ask you
a week earlier,
but her plans weren't confirmed yet.
I was afraid that if I asked
and the timelines didn't line up,
I'd blow our cover.
So I didn't dare say anything, you know?
So when did you confirm you'd come?
When did I confirm I was coming?
Pretty early.
Almost the same time.
We booked the tickets together.
She booked the ticket for me.
You two came together.
I was supposed
to take the same train as her,
but I missed it.
I came on the train by myself.
Then he scrambled for a ticket
and got one scheduled
to arrive 30 minutes later.
Did you get a seat?
Of course, I had a seat.
We both had seats originally.
This is so painful.
No, this is so amazing.
We were even video chatting last night,
and now I'm seeing her in person.
I can't get over this.
That's why I rarely
reply to your messages.
So I didn't figure out why.
I was just wondering...
Didn't you notice
that I didn't reply
to your messages today either?
No, I was really busy this afternoon.
Then when I finished, didn't I just...
Yeah. Earlier you asked
what I was doing,
and I said,
"I have to meet
an important client today."
So I was the important client, right?
And that photo of escargots
was taken a couple of days ago, right?
Yeah, it was filmed before.
I even asked her, "Are you eating?"
She said yes
and sent me a photo.
You are such a good liar.
Do you know how crazy this is?
As soon as...
I was in the car getting ready
to unload my luggage,
and then I saw him get out first.
I panicked for a second.
I almost ran into you guys.
You know?
I immediately walked away
without looking back.
I saw someone in red pants,
and I didn't dare glance again.
I hurried off as fast as I could.
You saw us both?
I saw you.
Are you happy?
I'm so happy that I could fly.
Fly then.
Fly.
What are you doing?
You've gone boneless.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's skip the meal for now.
Leave you two...
What are you talking about?
Speak properly.
I'm about to sweat.
Don't be like that.
Such a surprise.
Unbelievable.
Please tell us how you feel right now.
How do you feel?
On a scale of 0 to 10,
how would you
rate your feeling right now?
13.5.
What's the 3.5 for?
Why the 0.5?
Let's order first.
Hurry up, I'm starving.
Waiter.
The real waiter.
The real waiter can come in now.
Another one is coming in, right?
Let me see who else is here.
Liu is here.
Liu and Ruita are all here.
Then I was the one kept in the dark.
Hello, we'd like to order.
Let's eat.
Come on.
Welcome to Beijing, everyone.
Welcome, everyone.
Cheers.
Was it fun?
Fun.
Did you have fun?
I was pretty happy.
Wait.
This way, the next two days in Beijing,
you'll have way more fun.
You were only supposed
to hang out with us.
But now you don't have to stick with us.
Now...
Right.
Have you tried this?
What is this?
Just try it.
It's called Qianlong Cabbage.
Do you want this?
Do you want sweet garlic?
Yes.
Be careful, it's hot.
Xuan.
What's up?
We're just like this every day.
(Just eat up and enjoy our drinks)
Interesting.
Yeah.
How is it?
Your thoughts after the watch-along.
My thoughts after the watch-along.
Your dates with other girls
were really interesting to watch.
How often do you video call?
We usually do it at night mostly,
because we're both free.
We might...
Only do video calls, no voice calls?
Only video calls.
A video call would pop up right away?
Yes, just call straight away.
At first, we'd
pretend to be polite and ask,
"Can I video call you?"
Later, we just skipped all that
and called straight away.
How long do the calls last each time?
Super long calls.
Pretty long.
Last night,
we talked for over three hours,
almost four hours, right?
Video call?
But in my past relationships,
I never liked video chatting,
well.
Because we can't see each other
face-to-face.
Are you two in a relationship now?
I knew
you were going to ask that next.
We're thinking the same thing.
Are you two in a relationship now?
No.
So it's the pre-relationship stage.
I don't think we're
in the pre-relationship stage anymore.
What is the pre-relationship stage?
I don't know either.
I didn't understand.
Does the pre-relationship stage
mean two people really like each other
and are about
to get together right away?
I'll bite you.
Then I really don't know
whether we're
in this pre-relationship stage.
I think we did.
When was it?
(Day 10 after leaving the house)
I think it was after we left the house,
or during the last couple of days
in the house.
The house slowed down your pace.
So that's what you meant.
He was so cheeky yesterday.
When we were on video call yesterday...
Sorry. He was so cheeky.
When we were on video call yesterday,
I said, "Why do you
have forehead wrinkles?"
He said,
"Yes."
"You're so old, and you don't
have forehead wrinkles."
It made me so mad.
What are you talking about?
Sorry.
I just wanted to tease you a bit.
Keep your mouth shut.
You're the old one.
What he said made you upset.
That hurt so much.
No, it didn't.
I don't care.
After all, I don't have
forehead wrinkles.
Neither of you has them?
I do.
I've already got crow's feet.
I have them.
But they're covered by my hair.
Guys all have them.
Lizheng doesn't have any.
Lizheng must be really good
at taking care of himself.
He's young.
The young one is here.
Right.
I think Lizheng looks younger than me.
Indeed, no wonder he called you brother
for three days straight.
He asked me right at the start,
and I just
didn't want to explain.
Let's leave it at that.
So what is Liu doing now?
Do you want to video call her?
I'll try calling her.
(Waiting for Ruita)
Then I'll call Ruita.
(The subscriber you dialed is busy...)
She is probably getting a massage.
She ignored me.
You feel upset, right?
I'm about to cry.
Hello.
Coming.
Who are you?
Hi.
(On a call with Xu Lvyang...)
What are you doing?
I just got out of the shower,
and I'm drying my hair.
Liu, what do you usually
call Zhou Youling?
Baby?
(This is super sweet)
I call him Babe.
That's too much.
Then what do you call Liu?
I call her Baby.
Right, what do you guys
usually call each other?
I just call her Xuan.
You think...
I won't say it.
No.
Okay, there is something. Say it.
I said I call her Xuan.
No.
Her reaction says it's not.
Can I say it?
No.
She won't let me say it.
Say it.
Then you say the first character,
and we'll guess the last two.
Even just one single character is fine.
No.
This isn't good.
(Take a wild guess)
Rascal.
You rascal.
Something feels off.
How could we possibly say that?
You rascal.
Just say one word.
Here it comes, you rascal.
We can't say it.
No, do you two call each other
the same nicknames?
I just changed his WeChat nickname
(Weirdo Lad)
to Weirdo Lad.
Because he's always acting crazy.
(Ms. Contradiction)
Ms. Contradiction.
She always speaks in reverse.
Your nicknames are quite interesting.
Weirdo Lad.
Your nicknames
are totally straightforward.
Let me tell you.
We once
(See Episode 5 for details)
chatted until 5 AM
by the pool,
and everything she said
was the opposite of what she meant.
We just couldn't understand each other.
I'm hanging up first.
Why are you hanging up?
I have no makeup on.
No one's filming you.
You can flip the camera around
so she can check.
No one's filming you.
How will Zhuoran get here?
High-speed train, for sure.
How else is he supposed to get there?
You all call him by his full name.
Only I call him Dong.
It's weird for me to call him Dong.
I even call him Dong.
Then you guys should call me Xuan.
That's what you were planning.
You picked up on that fast.
How is it?
Almost.
Where am I staying?
You haven't decided yet.
None of us has decided, not even Xuan.
Thanks, boss.
Let's head out. Go back and rest early.
Let's go.
How many of us are there tomorrow?
If Zhuoran and Xihui both come,
it'll be seven people.
Let's find a place for tomorrow.
Okay.
(Shanghai)
Let's go to Wuzhen.
Let's go.
(Wuzhen Travel Diary:
Zhou Youling, Xu Lvyang)
We're here.
Let's go.
The weather is nice today.
Let's go. We're going
to the dye workshop in Wuzhen.
Experience it.
It's beautiful.
It is indeed pretty.
One for each, take an apron.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'll tie it for you.
Okay, help me tie this.
Okay.
Let's go.
Do you want a tie-dye pattern?
I like this kind.
I think tie-dye is all about
being free and casual overall.
Right.
Freestyle.
Yes.
Creation theme.
Go with the flow.
Then tell me, what's your theme?
My creation theme is...
What is it?
Flower.
Then my creation theme is
heart.
I feel like this one
is almost done.
And now I'm going to start...
You've already tied so many.
I want to tie it into little knots.
(No)
Make a rustic one.
It's okay.
How come they're all different?
It'll look better if they're different.
Do you think these two...
The size.
You want to make a rustic one?
Who is it for?
Who is it for, Mr. Zhou?
You make a rustic one.
Why make a rustic one?
What if it's not rustic?
Done.
Is my hair stuck together?
Is it?
No, just a little bit.
Do you want me to help you?
Help me fix my hair.
This side.
Okay, it hurts.
Chirp, chirp.
What?
Look, it's perfectly symmetrical,
four corners.
You've got a design.
Of course, I've got a design.
Wear two layers.
Your hands are too big.
My hands are like a kid's hands.
Okay.
Hold it.
Okay, let's go.
Mine is so pretty.
Total success.
It's so close to what I pictured.
I can't wait to see yours.
Time to witness a miracle.
Don't shake.
Let me see.
Where is the heart?
Bottom right corner.
What about the other side? Let me see.
Your pattern.
Looking at it this way. Yours is pretty.
I have both sides.
Do you have both sides?
Of course, I do.
Flip it over.
Let me see.
Same one. It also has both sides.
Feels like totally different styles.
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Leaving.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Let's take a photo together.
Let's hold hands.
Let's hold hands and take a photo first.
(Stiff)
Let's hold hands first.
It's good.
Wait for me.
What are you laughing at?
You're so funny.
You get all stiff
whenever you take photos.
It's so hilarious.
Looks good.
Get close to each other.
The girl shall press closer to the guy.
Lean your body up a bit.
Yeah, face more towards me.
Like this.
Put your left hand on his chest.
Yeah.
Sweet wife.
Guy, look over here
with a cool expression.
Okay.
Touch his chest muscles.
Come a little closer, guy.
You two give each other a quick kiss.
Really?
Look up.
No kiss.
Just a slight kiss, okay.
Yes.
No, I'll adjust your pose for you.
It's good now.
The lighting is really good now.
Yes.
I'm not, just shy.
Yes, very good.
Don't move.
Girl, a little bit shyer.
Looking at him, okay?
Yes.
Guy,
slightly touch her chin.
Switch hands.
Yes, the feeling of about to kiss.
So awkward.
Kiss slightly.
Yes, good.
A little more affectionate.
Again.
This is beautiful. Super beautiful.
Super pretty.
Pretty.
Girl, slowly kiss up a bit more.
Yes, very good.
Girl, close your eyes for a moment.
I haven't taken the close-up yet.
This doesn't need a close-up, right?
Very good.
Look at him.
Look up.
Yes, very good.
Go.
Yes, hold him.
Does it smell good?
Okay.
Come over here.
What's wrong?
You prefer to hold with your right hand?
Yes.
Men on the left,
women on the right, right?
Are you...
Isn't it, men on the left,
women on the right?
Yes.
Why is that?
Is there some obsession with this?
No obsession.
I'll throw you down.
Call out louder.
Pig's squeal.
The sun is really nice right now.
There's still a bit of light.
Quickly take a photo for you.
This one is actually okay too.
("Bossy CEO" starts his photography side hustle)
Let me take a couple for you.
Absolutely stunning.
I should do some creation here, right?
I think it automatically
lengthens things.
Really?
Absolutely stunning.
The feeling is coming back.
Can I stand a little higher?
Be careful.
Are you standing steady?
I can.
Just focus on your pose.
Absolutely stunning.
(Seriously creating)
Actually, this spot is pretty good too.
(Shot by Zhou Youling)
Absolutely stunning.
Amazing, this light.
My legs look so long.
Yeah, I found
an absolutely stunning scene.
You're amazing.
We almost missed it.
I was heading straight this way.
Right.
As soon as I saw this side,
the creative spark hit me.
I want to post those few today
without retouching.
Haven't you noticed that all photos
(A 'bossy CEO' production is always a masterpiece)
I take of you don't need retouching?
None of them need retouching.
But you said it could be better
with a little retouching.
But I don't think
that they need retouching.
Right, but a little retouching
would make it top-tier.
After others see it,
they'd want them as wallpaper.
Then why isn't it your wallpaper?
(When faced with a hard question, he just stops talking)
Digging your own grave.
Stir-fried chicken and river shrimp.
Let's eat spicy food.
Okay, let's eat spicy food.
Alright.
Cheers with chopsticks.
This is pickled vegetables
with bamboo shoots and edamame.
(Thoughtful)
Put it on your side.
It's just edamame.
Great.
Have you...
How many meals have you eaten
since leaving the house,
(Caring)
or eating alone?
I've only eaten twice.
Once with Ji Yu.
Once in Hainan.
And what else?
And then with you.
Which time?
The Snail Maiden.
(Thinking)
No.
(Giving more hints)
One-on-one,
ate at a restaurant.
Still can't remember?
Don't interrupt me.
It didn't happen in Hainan.
(Muttering)
In Hainan, I only ate with Ji Yu once.
After we came back,
(Memory returns)
Liyao Village.
(It's in Episode 8)
Looks great.
(Jealous mode activated)
What did you eat with Ji Yu that day?
You've asked so many times.
You've even asked Ji Yu.
(Caring)
Western food?
It wasn't exactly Western food.
It was just like a...
(Really cares)
What time did you go eat?
We probably started eating around six
and finished around seven.
Then we went for a walk by the sea.
After the walk,
we said
as you were having
your birthday that night,
so we headed back early to set up.
Talked about
how to celebrate my birthday?
What was your task?
To keep you occupied.
To keep you occupied after you got back
(Realization dawns)
and check if you had a phone on you.
So,
when I came back,
(Replaying the scene)
you rushed up to me immediately
to keep me occupied.
Another misunderstanding.
Eating this is making me so hot.
That was picking ten questions to answer.
What?
I mean
that (Love Actually) travel plan.
It's about picking
ten questions to answer.
I see.
Wait a minute.
(Q: The biggest regret)
The biggest regret.
What I wrote down was
not being brave enough
to express my feelings.
(Mr. Zhou is not satisfied)
That's a cop-out.
You wish I had written about you, right?
(Starting to coax)
What was your biggest regret?
I didn't confess
to Zhou Youling in person.
And what?
Which version of myself
do I want to affirm most?
The one I want to affirm most
is the version of me who,
after returning to Shanghai,
bravely asked Zhou Youling out, right?
Is it okay
to write it like that, Mister?
At least you should write like that.
If you didn't write it that way,
then forget it.
I won't write it that way either.
It goes well with rice.
Finished eating. Let's go.
Mr. Zhou,
for your visit to Wuzhen today,
have we been good hosts?
It's okay.
There's another activity.
Please look forward to it, Mr. Zhou.
(Beijing)
We've arrived at the place to eat now.
We are both absolutely starving.
It smells so good here.
It looks really delicious.
Angeli's beef fried sauce noodles.
Okay, thank you.
Shall I just mix it directly?
Is that okay?
You do it.
I'll send a photo to the group chat
to make them jealous.
I can already smell the aroma.
Thank you.
Let me take this away for you.
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
(You're being too formal)
Can we stop saying thank you?
Okay.
Thank you.
This is delicious.
That's Sautéed Pork Liver,
Pork Kidney and Pork Tenderloin.
But people in Wuhan
generally like spicy food.
I think Wuhan stir-fries are very spicy.
Yes.
What fun things are there
to do in Wuhan?
I'll take you to Yellow Crane Tower.
I'm not really into
visiting tourist spots.
But you took me
to visit tourist spots today.
Sorry.
What can couples actually do together?
What do you think we can do?
Isn't it just spending time
with each other,
eating and chatting?
What? Why are you laughing like that?
Why are you smiling like that?
Isn't it just eating, chatting,
and watching movies?
What else can you do on a date?
I feel like our time in the house,
the things we did were just...
Just a set of fixed routines
for everyone,
eating, chatting, and watching movies.
Right.
And then, yeah.
Maybe for me, I would add sports,
like playing ball
or working out together.
Yeah.
But I think
isn't life made up of these things?
Spending time together
and doing these things together.
Otherwise, there's no interaction.
Are you full?
Almost.
Let's go then.
Let's go.
Go.
Okay.
Let's head out!
The last time I was in Beijing
was really three years ago.
That's crazy.
What feeling does Beijing
give you?
Beijing feels a bit more formal to me.
My uncle is also in Beijing.
My uncle and aunt are also in Beijing.
I didn't even tell them I was coming.
Do you want to meet them?
You're silent.
No answer.
Let's go.
Punch it,
and new destination right now.
Let my uncle take a look first.
Is this a place for afternoon tea?
I don't know.
I think
I've been here.
I usually never come here.
It's too crowded.
You can barely move.
Then why did you bring me here?
To let you experience being a tourist.
The tourist vibe.
So I can barely move?
So you can barely move.
Unable to move.
Unable to stop.
What does "unable to stop" mean?
Unable to move and unable to stop
are two different things.
Don't lump them together.
Oh no, my IQ is failing me again.
Although being unable to stop
might lead to being unable to move.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
You're talking nonsense with me.
You started talking nonsense.
So I just played along
and talked nonsense.
No, I just thought of the phrase.
Can't I just say something random?
What's wrong with just saying it?
It's not like I'm doing anything.
Unable to stop, unable to move.
Unable to stop.
Stop...
"Stop" and shop.
(Sudden idiom chain)
Shop...
Shop what?
Stuck, aren't you?
Shop...
Dumbfounded huh?
Shop until you drop the ball.
Is that even a phrase?
Yes.
Shop until you drop the ball.
Ball...
Ballistic.
Ballistic missile.
'Idiot'.
Silly...
Silly-billy.
Silly-billy-ish.
Ish...
Silly-billy, ish...
No, it has to be "ish".
It's time for your episode again.
I know.
Time to take your medicine.
Darling, time to take your medicine.
Okay, you want me "dead".
I want to cure your illness.
Parking lot entrance.
Right.
Is that okay?
I've actually
never been to this street before.
I find it quite fresh, too.
I'm also an outsider.
Can we look at this?
Vintage?
Is it vintage?
Seems like it.
Let me ask you a question.
When we all watched the career clips,
(Q: Who are the two men you're most interested in now?)
it was me first, and then BK (Lu Bingkun).
Who are the two men
you're most interested in now?
Xiao Wentao, Lu Bingkun.
So what if BK (Lu Bingkun)
had taken the initiative
to approach you?
At the time,
I named two people randomly
to confuse everyone's perspective.
So, you
named us randomly?
Kind of.
One, yes,
the other, no.
So
BK (Lu Bingkun) was named randomly.
(Satisfied)
Really?
Yes.
Why?
Why did you name two people?
I was asked to name two people,
so I named two.
Do you think BK's age
is something you can't accept?
It's not that I can't accept it,
but the age gap
is indeed a bit too wide.
Have we already walked out?
We walked out,
but now we need to
circle around in that direction.
Can I put my phone in your pocket?
I really can't fit it into this bag.
And there's another question.
I remember I asked you.
I said,
"So, are you planning
to get to know anyone else?"
What did I say?
You said
you wanted to get to know Li Zheng.
I said that to you?
You were making that up, right?
I don't remember.
I was definitely making it up.
Sometimes I say randomly.
No.
I know why I said
I wanted to get to know Li Zheng.
Because earlier,
when you were on a date with Xihui,
Li Zheng was also left alone.
When we chatted
by the pool,
he asked me,
"So you've been getting to know
Xiao Wentao all along,
right?"
There wasn't much after that.
I went to the beach
for a stroll by myself.
You were messing around, right?
(Digging for answers)
So who were your top three options at the time?
What's with you today?
Because
there are a lot of things I don't know.
I want to find out.
I can know now.
Back then, you didn't have to tell me.
Then go watch my pre-interviews.
I'm learning from you.
(Speechless)
Go watch the show then.
Go watch it in June.
You're so annoying.
This is all how you treated me.
Isn't that exactly what you're like?
Just tell me about it.
In the first few days...
Was he constantly asking
about your...
What's in it for me if I tell you?
I'll tell you about mine.
(This conversation is going nowhere)
I don't want to know about yours.
I'll annoy you to "death".
Tell me, I want to know.
What do you want to know?
I want to know.
(Activating aegyo mode)
I'm very curious.
I mean
what they are called.
(Super naturally holding hands)
What are the two of them called?
Big Bro, Second Bro, right?
Still Big Bro, Second Bro.
Big Bro and Second Bro,
I think,
in this situation,
are definitely
the most attractive to the women.
They are both tall and handsome.
But I think you're handsome too.
Really? Oh, my God.
Really?
You're so fake.
Because in my heart,
I don't have a second or third place.
So it didn't matter
whoever I named.
Really, that's what I thought
in my mind.
Alright.
I'm fine now.
Okay.
I'm not fine.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
- I'm not.
- I'm really fine.
I'm not fine.
I'm really fine.
You're also fine.
How do you know I'm fine?
What's wrong? Tell me.
I have so many issues.
What?
What did you say?
What issues?
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Don't move.
Okay.
It fell down.
What thing?
Well,
the one that flies.
Be careful.
Are you trying to pinch me to "death"?
You may give me my phone.
No need.
You keep pulling up your pants.
In case it...
Really, no need.
Give it to me.
I'll stick it in this bag.
It's really fine.
It will fall.
It won't fall.
Give it to me.
No need, it's really fine.
Let's go.
You are so concerned with your image.
There's a kitten fishing up here.
I'm going to start creating.
Take your time creating.
I'll create for you.
Taking a picture of me?
Looks great.
Go back.
Put this flower here.
Wait.
Looks great.
Elegant.
Don't bite it.
Looks great.
One more photo.
Yes, looks great. Oh, my God.
Stand here.
Looks great.
This one.
You know how to take photos.
Since you know how, please take more.
Let's find a place to rest.
Let's find a place to sit for a bit.
I'm tired.
(Preview)
Let's stroll through Wuzhen in the early morning.
Yes.
This feeling is really nice.
Handsome.
Where is the willow tree?
We've arrived in the city.
Let's dig in.
Take a picture.
Make a heart sign.
Do you want to try some
of my round noodles?
Awesome, right?
Awesome.
Let me see yours.
Yours is not bad either.
Let's get a photoshoot done.
Are you happy, baby?
Do you want to wear a tank top
or a T-shirt?
A T-shirt.
A tank top. Do you have muscles?
I need to get a pump first.
Do a push-up right now.
That's too abstract.
I'm going to drink it.
Whose stinky feet smell is this?
If fees apply, just stop.
Whatever,
I'll quote you the price later.
Last night, I...
Never mind,
let's not talk about last night.
Does it look good?
A birthday gift for you.
You actually remembered this?